Three, two, one, yes!
We've been waiting for you.
Okay, so, Iyori, where am I?
Where am I?
Seino,
Hiroshima!
Yes!
It doesn't look like Hiroshima at all.
It's just a wall.
Just a wall.
I was in Hiroshima the day before, working for the Carp,
I was in Hiroshima, so Iyori came to Hiroshima to see me.
I came to see you.
Did you seem to be okay on the 4-hour bullet train?
I was sleeping with the manager the whole time.
It's been a long time since I've been here.
I wanted to travel to Hiroshima with Iyori, so I'm glad.
I'm glad.
But, unfortunately, I don't have the best plan in the history of Iyori's A.JOY channel.
I am undecided.
So, let's walk around Hiroshima and eat delicious food.
Eat.
What do you want to eat?
I'm hungry. I'm hungry. I want to eat anything. I want to eat meat, noodles, anything.
Then I'll feed you anything you want.
I'm off.
Don't follow me. Don't follow me.
What? What? What? What?
A heart.
Oh, no. I'm scared. I'm scared.
I'm listening.
Where are you?
Right now, I'm in a place called Alice's Garden in the center of Hiroshima.
Normally, it's not like this,
But today, there are like food stalls.
There are so many of them. They look delicious.
I've never seen them before.
Oh, wow! Is that so?
I see. So, let's go there.
Bunny.
Hello, there.
What is it? This.
Ramen noodles.
Don't follow me. Don't follow me.
What? What should we do?
I want to eat something.
Hey, hey, there's also fortune-telling. Fortune-telling!
Don't you like fortune-telling more than fortune-telling? I like fortune-telling. I look at it every day.
Hello. I'd like to ask you a favor.
May I? Please.
May I ask what you're looking for?
I just turned 26 years old recently.
I'm wondering what this past year will be like.
Because suddenly I can't stop being nervous.
I am nervous.
It's the year of my 26th year.
I'm in the midst of a major earthquake, and I'm in a dangerous relationship,
I'm at the point where my new life is going to change 180 degrees.
Yes, I am.
What we have experienced, what we have done together, what we have done together
We are developing more and more.
Another thing is that you will have to make decisions and do things on your own.
If you set a big goal and build the confidence to work toward it on your own, you will be able to make a fortunate human being.
If you make a big goal and build up the confidence to work toward it alone, you will become a lucky person.
It's amazing.
There are people who say that happiness is not like that in the first place.
I see charisma, and I also see public roles, acting, and so on.
Congratulations.
I am happy for you.
There is one thing I want to say. I'm a little unsure.
Be confident.
Yes, I am.
That's great.
Do you have one?
Four.
Oh, I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. Wait a minute.
Can I be happy?
Yes. Well, let's try something a little more interesting.
Let's try something a little more interesting.
You get to choose.
Does it depend on my relatives?
Yes. Choose one of them.
That one?
Two choices. Oh, shit.
This one.
This one?
Yes. Then take a look.
Is it there?
Yes.
The Empress card.
The Empress?
Yes. The card of the Empress is the card of a woman's ally. It is the card of having a goal and developing that goal.
It is a card that tells us that we have a goal, and that goal will grow and develop.
Therefore, it does not mean that you will be happy right away, but rather that you will be perfectly happy when you have gained experience little by little and have found what happiness means to you.
It means that if you follow the path of your goal, you will be happy.
That's what it means.
I am happy.
I'm happy.
I can be happy.
I'll be fine. I'm happy.
I'm glad we're not here.
What? What? What card?
I'm shooting this video right now, and it's the most open-ended project in the history of the project.
Will it get more views?
Tell me I don't have to watch it.
You did.
Because the power of the two of us today is on the video, you have to watch it.
Is there any lucky food today?
I'm going to go.
I'm thinking something a little fluffy.
Fluffy.
Maybe something like cotton balls or something like that.
I see.
What's in the back?
This is a meat type.
Yay!
Let's order this snack.
I want some. I'm hungry.
What do you want?
I got cotton candy!
I have cotton candy!
I got cotton balls!
There's a cotton ball!
What a surprise, we found a cotton ball!
Yay!
Good evening. Do you have a chance to be here by chance?
No, I don't.
That's not good.
If we eat both of them, it means we're going to have a good day on location.
That's right. Next time you'll grow up, right?
That's right.
Please look at them a lot.
I'll eat.
Are you used to it?
Are you a good glider?
I got it.
You having fun?
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Oh, that's good.
I got a cotton ball!
Yay!
I'm good! I knew it.
This kind of art seems to exist. Fantastic.
Bon appétit.
I hope today's location shooting will be successful. That's why I brought this.
Uma!
We're going to run out.
It's delicious.
I knew it! It's freshly made and fluffy.
It's amazing.
It's in Hiroshima dialect,
Hiroshima dialect?
I was here yesterday, too, so it's really Hiroshima dialect.
Really? You thought so this morning?
I've been thinking it since I was talking to your father.
Really?
When you talk to people with Hiroshima dialect, you probably get it.
That's great.
After that, we'll see what we do.
Meat!
Eat meat, meat, meat, meat.
That's right. If Yuri doesn't eat meat, that's it.
Meat?
Meat. Meat.
Chacha-chacha.
Christmas tree.
Let's go to the other side.
Call it Hondori in Hiroshima,
It says "Hondori Street" there.
There it is?
Yes, it is.
This is the place I've been going to since I was a student,
I have passed by this place many, many times since I was a student.
Yes, there is a jump-jump-jump.
Jump, jump, jump, jump, jump.
Jump jump jump jump.
Jump, jump, jump, jump, jump, jump, jump, jump, jump, jump.
What? There's everything here.
This is a town for young people.
Eat, eat, eat.
Gesen, huh?
Gesen. Or Tokyo.
Can I eat?
Sure. Let's take Purikura.
Yes, yes, yes.
I always take purikura with my friends here,
I'd like to take Purikura with my friends.
I'm going to meet my favorite person, the one with the mascara.
Look!
Taiko!
Which one's back there?
Here, too!
Oyster!
Oysters!
It's just like Hiroshima.
It's very popular.
Yes, it is.
It's all over the news and social networking sites.
Congratulations!
That's great!
You want to do it, too? I wanna do it!
Can I? Sure!
Take it off! Don't look at my wallet.
I'm not showing you my wallet.
Wait! I only have 100 yen!
I want baby boom-boom-boom!
That's why I want this baby.
Okay, Anna, I'll take this one.
Why not? That's why I'm scared.
I mean, this is the only way, right?
But if I take this one... Please! Please! Please! Please! Please! Please! Please! Please!
I don't like the idea of bumping into it.
You're right.
Oh...
Aah! I can do it!
Aah! Aah!
Yeah! Yeah!
I'm home! I'm home!
Yeah! You're so cute!
High five! High five!
But it's only 300 yen!
That was $700.
How to win! Winning tips!
Any of these will do, right?
Yeah! Okay!
Okay!
What's it gonna be like?
You know, I'm really nervous.
This is also an Ohtake!
Uhhh...
Three, two, one.
Hey, hey, that's Kaki.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, persimmon!
Next, next, next, next.
What are you doing?
Three, two, one.
I'm not getting a reaction from my face, am I?
What about you, Kaki?
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Oh, no, no, no!
Let's get the last shot of me, Kaki!
My Kaki!
Three, two, one.
No way!
No!
Kaki!
For the first time in my life, I'm alone.
He's so cute!
She's so pretty!
Kaki didn't fit in.
Here it comes!
At Pricky's place where I used to go when I was a student.
I finally got a shot!
I'm so happy!
I love this Anna!
I'm all alone now.
I found something that looks really delicious.
Isn't this a Hiroshima specialty store?
Can I come in?
Hiroshima Products Store
We have a lot of things from Hiroshima.
What's so interesting?
Everything! Take a look.
I want some!
You like Mayuka, right?
I like Hitomi, too.
This is very famous in Hiroshima.
Really?
There's Onomichi Ramen, too.
Onomichi?
You've surpassed us all on your own.
He's got a lot of stuff.
I bet this is good, too.
Delicious!
That's what happens when you go on a shopping date with Yori.
I only go to Len's.
Look! Our favorite!
This is delicious!
I love collaborations!
I know they sell them at the convenience store.
I dream of one day
I dream to collaborate with this place someday!
I'm looking forward to it!
I bought it!
Souvenirs for everyone!
I'm buying for the members.
I'll put them in the lesson room.
This is an o-hagi shop.
It's famous in Hiroshima.
You like o-hagi?
I'm here.
Ankoro
This is Ankoro.
And this one too.
This is Ankoro, too.
Ta-da!
chuka soba
Chuka Soba!
This is the famous "Chikara" restaurant!
It smells so good!
Bon appétit!
[Hajime Shacho's ending]
Umami! It's so good!
I'm so glad it's so flavorful!
I love the consistency of the noodles!
Really? I love it!
I'm so lucky to be able to eat this!
Wheat Wheat Wheat
Wheat... wheat... wheat... wheat... wheat...
You used to eat it?
I used to eat it.
I love it.
It's not o-hagi, it's yakko.
Bon appétit.
Yum, yum, yum!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The rice is a little firm.
Ah, ah, octopus!
I love chihuahua!
Don't you? That's why I said it.
You told me about the chi- moo.
Yes, I knew you'd love it.
And when you told me...
I already knew.
As you can imagine.
And, as expected...
I knew it!
The name of this place is "Tempura Momiji".
I'm the MV here too.
And I think I used the "koshian" in the music video.
I think it was used in the music video.
They have lemon, chocolate, green tea, cream, and koshian (sweet bean paste).
What would you like?
But I also want a Chi-Mo.
I've been trying to stay here.
I don't know.
I don't know if you can see it, but...
But you've been doing this for a long time, right?
While talking.
And he touches his fingernails so much.
It's absolutely disgusting, isn't it?
He was doing this to me the whole time I was down there.
He was trying to figure out what it tasted like.
You don't like it?
I love it!
I'm so happy!
Oh, my God!
You're so cute! It's okay! You can drink it!
Delicious! Bon appétit!
Yum!
Looks good.
It's really good! Cold! It's cold!
That's for sure.
Get the lemon!
Tempura Momiji
Bon appétit! Cheers!
Yum!
Freshly fried food tastes good, doesn't it?
Hot!
Lemon? Lemon, but sweet!
Yum!
Anko? Anko!
Anko is red bean paste.
It's also called a pikatzk, right?
Are you happy? So is Anko.
Anko's happy to be eaten by you.
Is that possible?
Heart!
And so we come to the okonomiyaki shop!
Yay!
We can finally eat okonomiyaki! Yay! I'm so excited!
There are so many different okonomiyaki restaurants in this okonomiyaki shop!
Wow!
There are many okonomiyaki shops here.
Yes!
Today we are going to visit
Dandan!
Tetsu-san!
Let's get going! Yeah!
I'll be right back!
I want some, I want some, I want some!
Well, what should I do?
Soba or udon first?
Oh, I don't know.
Thank you so much!
Thank you very much!
Now I'm trying to decide between soba and udon.
I'm having a hard time deciding.
What?
Stop eating already!
Stop, stop, stop!
I've decided.
All right!
I'll have a bowl of soba noodles with meatballs
One with green onion
One soba with green onion and one...
Soba noodles with meat and egg
Ika-tamago toppings
I'll have a small portion of both.
Both small.
Here, it's my service.
So kind.
Can we eat then?
We can eat.
Can you go ahead and eat?
We can go.
Okay. I'll just go to the normal place.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching.
Ladies and gentlemen, I have an announcement to make.
It's warm and I'm sleepy.
Beautiful circle.
It's a beautiful circle.
I'm going to turn it over.
Yoo-hoo!
Plenty of wolfsbane sauce.
Here it comes!
It's so good!
Bon appétit!
I put hot juice in it.
Delicious.
How is it?
Very, very, very good.
When you come to Hiroshima, you have to try okonomiyaki.
Okonomiyaki.
I topped it with green onions for the first time.
It's good to practice again.
Delicious!
Gentle taste.
It tastes soft.
Yes, sir.
I got it
Bon appétit
Thank you for the food
It was delicious!
Everyone should come and try it!
Come on, Mr. Iyori!
The last stop today
We are here at the Hiroshima Drimination!
Yay!
Let's take some pictures and stuff.
Let's go!
Let's go on a balloon ride.
We can? Oh, my God.
It's a balloon.
Can you put one on my feet, too?
Thank you. - Thank you.
Apple, apple, green apple?
Oh, carrots! And a rabbit! It's a beaselfish!
A beancel fish!
Rabbits and carrots.
It's a beancel fish!
Beasel!
Yeah!
Beautiful, isn't it?
I love it! Nice! What the hell are you!
Nice picture!
Nice!
That's great!
It's great!
Very beautiful!
You're a good photographer!
You're good!
That's what I'm talking about!
You're so good!
I heard that passing through this circle makes you very happy!
Really?
Yes!
I just made it!
You made it! You made it!
You made it!
Let's be happy together!
Let's be together!
Dedede de de de de go!
Ta-da!
It's big!
Where is it?
Look!
Wow!
Ours! Isn't this one so much funnier?
It's so big!
It's so warped!
Well, today we enjoyed the whole day together in Hiroshima!
It was fun!
Really? But now, it's time to go home!
Time to go home?
That's it!
But it's been a great day.
I've been having fun before I came here, and I'll be having fun when I leave!
Yay!
It was like a private party!
It was like we really came to eat together! Hiroshima!
Are you okay?
It was fun!
I wish my fans could come to Hiroshima!
Yeah! Let's come together! Hiroshima!
I want to go to Iyori's hometown too!
I want you to come!
Well then, thank you for watching!
Bye bye!